import { Question } from "./classes";

// random trivia questions with numerical answers
export const triviaQuestions = [
    {
        question: "In what year did the United States enter World War II?",
        answer: "1941"
    },

    {
        question: "How many players are there on a regulation basketball team?",
        answer: "5"
    },

    {
        question: "How many states are there in the United States?",
        answer: "50"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the highest score possible in a game of ten-pin bowling?",
        answer: "300"
    },

    {
        question: "How many moons does the planet Earth have?",
        answer: "1"
    },

    {
        question: "How many legs does a spider have?",
        answer: "8"
    },

    {
        question: "How many strings does a standard guitar have?",
        answer: "6"
    },

    {
        question: "How many times has the United States won the FIFA World Cup?",
        answer: "1"
    },

    {
        question: "How many ounces are in a pound?",
        answer: "16"
    },

    {
        question: "How many sides does a hexagon have?",
        answer: "6"
    }
]

export const aiQuestions =
    [
        { question: "How many keys are on a traditional piano?", answer: "88" },
        { question: "How many countries make up the United Kingdom?", answer: "4" },
        { question: "How many players does a baseball team have on the field?", answer: "9" },
        { question: "How many teeth do adult humans have?", answer: "32" },
        { question: "How many time zones are there in the world?", answer: "24" },
        { question: "How many ounces are in a pound?", answer: "16" },
        { question: "How many protons are in a gold atom?", answer: "79" },
        { question: "How many seconds are in a day?", answer: "86400" },
        { question: "How many players are on a soccer team?", answer: "11" },
        { question: "How many elements are on the periodic table?", answer: "118" },
        { question: "How many bones are in the human body?", answer: "206" },
        { question: "How many players are on a football team?", answer: "11" },
        { question: "How many chromosomes are in a human cell?", answer: "46" },
        { question: "How many oceans are there in the world?", answer: "5" },
        { question: "How many teaspoons are in a tablespoon?", answer: "3" },
        { question: "How many bones are in the human hand?", answer: "27" },
        { question: "How many legs do shrimp have?", answer: "10" },
    ]

export const witsQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What percent of Americans have never traveled outside of their home state?",
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults use the Internet?",
        answer: "90"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of Americans went to the beach in the past year?",
        answer: "48"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults have a tattoo?",
        answer: "21"
    },
    {
        question: "How many bathrooms does the White House have?",
        answer: "35"
    },
    {
        question: "How many Starbucks restaurants are there in the US?",
        answer: "15149 "
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American women dye their hair?",
        answer: "75"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of home fires start in the kitchen?",
        answer: "49"
    },
    {
        question: "On average, how many days per year does it rain in Las Vegas?",
        answer: "27"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of domestic households own a pet?",
        answer: "67"
    },
    {
        question: "In US dollars, how much did the US pay Russia for the Alaska purchase in 1867?",
        answer: "7200000"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of Americans use some sort of vision correction?",
        answer: "75"
    },
    {
        question: "How many US states are in more than one timezone?",
        answer: "13"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American households had cable or satellite TV in 2019?",
        answer: "73"
    },
    {
        question: "What was the estimated population of the United States in July of 1776?",
        answer: "2500000"
    },
    {
        question: "How many US states have a town named 'Springfield'?",
        answer: "34"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults are married?",
        answer: "38"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults have never been in an airplane?",
        answer: "13"
    },
    {
        question: "On average, how many bottles of wine does an American adult drink per year?",
        answer: "13"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of Harvard students are international students?",
        answer: "21"
    },
    {
        question: "How many US states have a population above 5 millions?",
        answer: "23"
    },
    {
        question: "How many times did the US host the Olympic Games?",
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "On average, how many BigMacs does a McDonald's restaurant sell per day in the US?",
        answer: "106"
    },
    {
        question: "Over the last 100 years, how many years was 'Michael' the most popular baby name for a male in the United States?",
        answer: "44"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of Americans consider baseball their favorite sport to watch?",
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "On average, how much does an American spend on clothes every year (in US dollars)?",
        answer: "972"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American presidents have died while occupying that role?",
        answer: "18"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults have drank alcool in the past year?",
        answer: "70"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the American army is female?",
        answer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "How many states border an ocean?",
        answer: "23"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of Harvard students went to high school in a public school?",
        answer: "63"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults have consulted a doctor in the past year?",
        answer: "84"
    },
    {
        question: "How many US states have a higher cattle population than their human population?",
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "On average, how many pairs of shoes does an American woman own?",
        answer: "19"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults smoke?",
        answer: "20.6"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year were the roller skates invented?",
        answer: "1759"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of Americans have been to Alaska?",
        answer: "13"
    },
    {
        question: "How much did Elvis pay for Graceland in 1957?",
        answer: "103500"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American children hang a stocking at Christmas?",
        answer: "29"
    },
    {
        question: "How many U.S. states legally allow first cousins to get married?",
        answer: "25"
    },
    {
        question: "How many words does the average American speak per day?",
        answer: "15942"
    },
    {
        question: "How much does the average American adult spend on lottery tickets each year?",
        answer: "248"
    },
    {
        question: "On average, how many greeting cards does a U.S. household purchase each year?",
        answer: "30"
    },
    {
        question: "How many nuclear power reactors are operating in the U.S.?",
        answer: "104"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults volunteered at least once in the past year?",
        answer: "26"
    },
    {
        question: "On average, how many days per year does it rain in Seattle?",
        answer: "150"
    },
    {
        question: "How many countries border the Mediterranean Sea?",
        answer: "21"
    },
    {
        question: "How many countries are there in Africa?",
        answer: "54"
    },
    {
        question: "How many billionaires are there in the world?",
        answer: "2153"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the world's rice is consumed in China?",
        answer: "30"
    },
    {
        question: "How many babies are born every minute in the world?",
        answer: "258"
    },
    {
        question: "There are 194 countries in the world. How many have French as an official language?",
        answer: "29"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the world population has blue eyes?",
        answer: "17"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the world population had Internet access in January 2020?",
        answer: "59"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the world population did not have electricity in 2020?",
        answer: "16"
    },
    {
        question: "In how many countries is there at least one KFC restaurant?",
        answer: "150"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the world population is vegetarian?",
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "How many persons have climbed Mount Everest during the year 2018?",
        answer: "807"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the world population owned a cellphone in 2019?",
        answer: "68"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the world population speak three languages or more?",
        answer: "16"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the world population is lactose intolerant?",
        answer: "65"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of the world population lives in Africa?",
        answer: "17"
    },
    {
        question: "How many people could be seated in the ancient Roman Colosseum?",
        answer: "49000"
    },
    {
        question: "In the Simpsons, how many different jobs did Homer have in the first 400 episodes?",
        answer: "188"
    },
    {
        question: "In the movie Return of the Jedi, what is Yoda's age?",
        answer: "900"
    },
    {
        question: "How many stars were on the Hollywood Walk of Fame in December 2019?",
        answer: "2690"
    },
    {
        question: "How many movies have been directed by Steven Spielberg before January 2020?",
        answer: "32"
    },
    {
        question: "How many characters die on screen in total during the eight seasons of Game of Thrones?",
        answer: "5863"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults have seen the movie 'Titanic'?",
        answer: "85"
    },
    {
        question: "In the Simpsons, what percent of all the dialogues are said by Homer?",
        answer: "21"
    },
    {
        question: "How many different villains were featured on the 60's Batman TV show?",
        answer: "30"
    },
    {
        question: "How many women did Jerry Seinfeld date in the TV series Seinfeld?",
        answer: "73"
    },
    {
        question: "In miles per hour, what speed does the DeLorean need to reach to time travel in the film Back to the Future?",
        answer: "88"
    },
    {
        question: "How many stars surround the mountain in the Paramount Pictures logo?",
        answer: "22"
    },
    {
        question: "How many novels were published by Stephen King by January 2020?",
        answer: "63"
    },
    {
        question: "How many different Pokemon were there in January 2020?",
        answer: "807"
    },
    {
        question: "Finland has a population of 5.2 millions. How many metal bands does that country have?",
        answer: "2825"
    },
    {
        question: "How many different games were released for the 80's Nintendo Entertainment System?",
        answer: "714"
    },
    {
        question: "How many coins in total are in the first Super Mario Bros game (1983)?",
        answer: "1089"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year was the novel Dracula first published?",
        answer: "1897"
    },
    {
        question: "How many James Bond novels did Ian Fleming write?",
        answer: "12"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year did Donald Duck first appear in a cartoon?",
        answer: "1934"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year was the Mr. Potato Head toy introduced?",
        answer: "1952"
    },
    {
        question: "How many times does Paul McCartney sing the phrase 'let it be' in The Beatles' song Let it be?",
        answer: "41"
    },
    {
        question: "How many territories are on a Risk board?",
        answer: "42"
    },
    {
        question: "How many times has Michael Jordan appeared on the cover of Sports Illustrated?",
        answer: "50"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year was ping pong invented?",
        answer: "1901"
    },
    {
        question: "How many PGA Tours did Tiger Woods win during his career?",
        answer: "81"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of American adults have played golf in 2019?",
        answer: "8.2"
    },
    {
        question: "How many different sports were featured during the Rio 2016 Summer Olympics?",
        answer: "28"
    },
    {
        question: "How many points did Michael Jordan score during his 15-season NBA career?",
        answer: "32292"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year was instant replay first used in a televised football game?",
        answer: "1963"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of Mike Tyson's fights were wins by knockout?",
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the record for the most seasons played by an NFL football player?",
        answer: "26"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year did Cassius Clay change his name to Muhammad Ali?",
        answer: "1964"
    },
    {
        question: "How many persons have ever been on the moon?",
        answer: "12"
    },
    {
        question: "How many minutes does an average Facebook user spends on the platform per day?",
        answer: "58"
    },
    {
        question: "How many satellites orbit the Earth?",
        answer: "2218"
    },
    {
        question: "How many minutes was the longest spacewalk ever by an astronaut?",
        answer: "536"
    },
    {
        question: "What percent of people has forgotten a password and had to reset it within the last 90 days?",
        answer: "78"
    },
    {
        question: "The most common password in the world is '123456'. What percent of people use it?",
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "Have many countries produce nuclear power?",
        answer: "31"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year was the very first email sent?",
        answer: "1971"
    },
]